export const data = [
  {
    question: "Who is known as the 'God of Cricket'?",
    option1: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    option2: "Virat Kohli",
    option3: "Ricky Ponting",
    option4: "Brian Lara",
    ans: 1, // Sachin Tendulkar
  },
  {
    question: "Which country has won the most ICC Cricket World Cups?",
    option1: "India",
    option2: "Australia",
    option3: "West Indies",
    option4: "England",
    ans: 2, // Australia
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who has scored the fastest century in One Day Internationals (ODIs)?",
    option1: "AB de Villiers",
    option2: "Chris Gayle",
    option3: "Shahid Afridi",
    option4: "Virat Kohli",
    ans: 1, // AB de Villiers
  },
  {
    question: "Who is the highest run-scorer in Test cricket?",
    option1: "Ricky Ponting",
    option2: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    option3: "Kumar Sangakkara",
    option4: "Jacques Kallis",
    ans: 2, // Sachin Tendulkar
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which bowler has taken the most wickets in international cricket?",
    option1: "Muttiah Muralitharan",
    option2: "Shane Warne",
    option3: "Anil Kumble",
    option4: "Glenn McGrath",
    ans: 1, // Muttiah Muralitharan
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who holds the record for the highest individual score in Test cricket?",
    option1: "Brian Lara",
    option2: "Matthew Hayden",
    option3: "Don Bradman",
    option4: "Virender Sehwag",
    ans: 1, // Brian Lara
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which player has scored the most centuries in international cricket?",
    option1: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    option2: "Virat Kohli",
    option3: "Ricky Ponting",
    option4: "Jacques Kallis",
    ans: 1, // Sachin Tendulkar
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who is the only player to score 400 runs in a single Test innings?",
    option1: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    option2: "Ricky Ponting",
    option3: "Brian Lara",
    option4: "Matthew Hayden",
    ans: 3, // Brian Lara
  },
  {
    question: "Which team won the first-ever T20 World Cup?",
    option1: "India",
    option2: "Pakistan",
    option3: "Sri Lanka",
    option4: "West Indies",
    ans: 1, // India
  },
  {
    question:
      "Who was the captain of the Indian cricket team when they won the 1983 Cricket World Cup?",
    option1: "Kapil Dev",
    option2: "Sachin Tendulkar",
    option3: "Sunil Gavaskar",
    option4: "MS Dhoni",
    ans: 1, // Kapil Dev
  },
  // Add more questions here
];
